bettor.com 2014-03-27

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Bettor.com is the trading name of Bettor.com, 0 whose registered office is at Bettor.com  
CL Services N.V.  
The Beach House  
Bapor Kibra z/n  
Willemstad  
Curaçao  
Willemstad  

Bettor.com takes your right to privacy extremely seriously and would like to assure any visitor to our website that the security of the personal information you provide to us is of paramount importance. In order to meet this responsibility we have put in place an exceptional Information Security Management System that will be systematically reviewed to ensure that our levels of protection are of the highest possible standard. You are under no obligation to divulge any Personal Information in relation to yourself. However, should certain information not be supplied then some of the services that we offer may not be available.

The types of personal information you would provide may include your name, address, date of birth, credit and/or debit card details, specifics of betting transactions, betting account details and any other data you may to choose to furnish us with. Bettor.com will at all times strive to ensure that any business operation involving the use of personal information will conform to the privacy regulations observed by any and all countries of operation. To this end the chief goal of this policy statement is to outline your rights of privacy and further set out how Bettor.com aims to protect them. Should any of your given personal information need to be changed, we provide you with the function to access and amend your details.

All references to "Bettor" or "the Group" within this policy statement include Ibetx Ltd and all of its direct or indirect subsidiaries, partners and their related companies wherever located in the world that may exist from time to time.

**_Collection of Personal Information_**

**Public**

Upon registering your Bettor.com account, you will be required to furnish us with certain personal information. In requesting information related to our products and services you may voluntarily provide us with additional personal information.

**Private**

Existing Bettor.com account holders must enter a username and password to gain access to the website. Customers are then able to place, cancel, modify or view their bets in the exchange or to view their personal information. To allow customers the freedom to leave and later return to our website without having to re-enter their details, 'Session Cookies' are built into the system. Web servers are also utilised to record all of the actions taken and pages visited during sessions.

In order for us to provide a high standard of service Bettor.com will monitor and record all types of communication you have with us be it in writing, by phone or by some means of electronic messaging. **It should be noted that our email, either to or from our website, is not encrypted so we strongly advise that,** with the exception of certain basic data such as names or usernames, you do not send us personal information in this manner. Any Personal Information that is sent in this way is done so at the users own risk.

**_Cookies and the Data They Provide_**

We use three main types of Cookies on our website, these are:

**Session Cookies**

These enable you to transfer data across the different pages of our website without the need to re-enter details. All registered customers will also have access to their stored personal information.

**Persistent Cookies**

These aid in establishing customers account names, name, email address, location (geographic and computer IP address) etc. as well as providing unique content and offers that are specific to their needs. We are also able to create an information flow that we can better understand how our website is being used and therefore how it might be improved in terms of design and layout.

**Third Party Cookies**

Certain third parties provide cookies through this website which are utilised for the tracking and success of advertising campaigns, the frequency with which customers are viewing specific advertisements, matching specific content to interests of customers, recording numbers of guest users visiting the website and for analysis of customers' internet use.

All cookies are capable of being disabled or enabled through altering the settings on your internet browser. The disabling of cookies may, however, mean some of the services that we offer may not be available.

**_Web Beacons_**

Some of the pages on our website will feature web beacons. Essentially these are electronic images that enable us to record the levels of users visiting our pages. These beacons store only minor information such as date/time stamps of page views and a description of the page where the beacon sits. Third party beacons can be placed by advertisers and are used to gauge the success of a specific advertisement.

**_Use of Personal Information_**

All processing of personal information will be performed in accordance with the relevant Data Protection laws and legislation. On registration, your information is stored in our database. This means that your personal information may be transferred outside the European Economic Area (EEA) to jurisdictions that may not provide the same level of protection and security procedures as the UK. Personal Information will be used only for these stated reasons:

Administering your account, maintenance of our own accounts and records, scrutiny of our standards of service, providing information of specific products and services and monitoring the use of our website. 

Any person not wishing to receive marketing, promotional or sales information may notify us of this through any of the methods outlined on our 'Contact Us' page. As soon as is reasonably possible your details will be eradicated from our databases.

Bettor.com will monitor and analyse any personal information it deems necessary to investigate criminal activity of any kind or, with regard to markets carried on our website, any means of compromising the integrity of that market or the rules by which it is governed through the relevant sporting authorities. All rights regarding the manner, in which Bettor.com records personal information, particularly copyright and database rights, are and will remain its property.

All users consent to the recording and monitoring of telephone calls and analysis of the betting information held on individual customers. 

To Whom May Personal Information Be Disclosed

Personal information may be transferred or disclosed to any company that is part of Ibetx Limited who we consider best able to perform the functions above. Bettor.com may also, from time to time, retain third parties to process personal information for the purposes outlined above with such processing governed by a contract in the form required by Law.

Personal information will not be revealed to any other user of our website but may be disclosed, if required, to an applicable government, regulatory or enforcement authority in connection with upholding the integrity or protecting the rules of a market or the prevention or detection of criminal activity. These authorities may use your personal information to investigate and act on any such transgressions in line with their own procedures.

**_User Consent_**

In providing us with personal information when registering with us or logging in to our website you consent to Bettor.com processing and disclosing personal information for the purposes that have been outlined in this Privacy Policy. Any user wishing to limit or modify their consent in any way should notify us of their intention through one of the methods outlined on our 'Contact Us' page.

**_Access to Personal Information_**

You may request, at any time, a copy of your Personal Information held by Bettor.com.

Bettor.com reserves the right to amend the Privacy Policy including changing the reasons for which it processes your personal information. Should Bettor.com deem it necessary to make such a change the Privacy Policy will be updated accordingly and posted on the website. Users continuing to access the website will be regarded as having accepted the revised Privacy Policy.

Any user wishing to get in touch regarding our Privacy Policy or Data Protection Policy should notify us through one of the methods outlined on our 'Contact Us' page.

**_Content_**

This section describes the policies and procedures followed by Bettor.com regarding all information shared on blogs, comments, questions, answers and polls. For all information shared on Bettor.com you consent to its collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses as described in this Privacy Policy.

A principal factor in using Bettor.com is to share content with others. By sharing this content you agree that this is information you want to be made public. This includes not only your blogs, comments, questions and answers, but also what polls you have created and voted on, the markets that you visit, the members you follow, the members who follow you and any photos uploaded to your profile.

**_Changes to This Policy_**

We may from time to time revise this Privacy Policy. The most current version of the policy will always be found at http://www.bettor.com/info/privacy-policy. We would also notify you should any critical changes be made to this policy either on the Bettor.com homepage or via the email associated with your account. By continuing to use our services after any changes become effective, you agree to abide by the revised Privacy Policy.
